<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">KatalogFilm2</string>
    <string name="title_activity_list_movie">ListMovie</string>

    <string name="title_avengerinfinity">Avengers: Infinity War (2018)</string>
    <string name="title_black_panther">Black Panther (2018)</string>
    <string name="title_rampage">Rampage (2018)</string>
    <string name="title_mission_imposible">Mission Imposible : Fallout (2018)</string>
    <string name="title_ready_player_one">Ready Player One (2018)</string>
    <string name="title_the_meg">The Meg (2018)</string>
    <string name="title_aquaman">Aquaman (2018)</string>
    <string name="title_jurassic_world">Jurassic World : Fallen Kingdom (2018)</string>
    <string name="title_incredibles2">INCREDIBLES 2 (2018)</string>
    <string name="title_deadpool2">Deadpool 2(2018)</string>
    <string name="title_star_wars">Solo : Star War Story (2018)</string>
    <string name="title_ant_man">Ant Man and The Wasp (2018)</string>
    <string name="title_predator">Predator (2018)</string>
    <string name="title_skyscraper">SKYSCRAPER (2018)</string>
    <string name="title_alpha">ALPHA (2019)</string>
    <string name="title_oceans8">Ocean\'s 8 (2018)</string>
    <string name="title_bumblebee">Bumblebee The Movie (2018)</string>
    <string name="title_strong">STRONG (2018)</string>
    <string name="title_robin_hood">Robin Hood (2018)</string>
    <string name="title_alita_battle_angel">Alita Battle Angel (2018)</string>

    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="overview_avengerinfinity">Avengers: Infinity War is one of the sequel films adopted from the superhero marvel comics by Stan Lee and Jack Kirby. Carrying the superhero fantasy genre, the American film, released in late April 2018, successfully became the fourth best-selling film in America and became the first superhero film to reach more than $ 2 billion worldwide. Infinity War directed by Anthony and Joe Russo is a continuation of The Avengers (2012) and also Avengers: Age of Ultron (2015). In this series the Avengers are joined by The Guardians of the Galaxy, and tries to stop Thanos in his efforts to collect powerful objects called Infinity Stones.</string>
    <string name="overview_black_panther">Another movie character from the comic Marvel by Stan Lee and Jack Kirby, who successfully starred in the box office, Black Panther.This American superhero film with action, drama, Sci-Fi genre tells the continuation of the story of Captain America: Civil War (2016). King TChalla who returned to his home in Wakanda country to become a new leader, had to find opposition from various factions.And in the midst of an enemy conspiracy to drag Wakanda in world war, the Black Panther who is a hero figure then cooperates with Wakanda special forces and C.I.A. agentsRyan Cooglers film was released theatrically in the United States on February 16, 2018 and received a lot of praise in terms of production, although the effects produced many received criticism.</string>
    <string name="overview_rampage">The monster Sci-Fi film, Rampage, is an American action adventure film based on the 1980 arcade video game series titled Midway Games. Rampage tells the story of George, an albino gorilla who was rescued from hunting by Davis Okoye, who was a primate expert and former American army special force. But due to evil experiments, George then mutated into an aggressive giant over time.While Davis Okoye tried to calm George, a mercenary named Claire instead made George and the two other monsters (wolves and crocodiles who also mutated) become increasingly aggressive in destroying the city.Despite criticism of the screenplay, the film, directed by Brad Peyton and Dwayne Johnson (as Davis Okoye), has grossed more than $ 426 million since it was released on April 13, 2018.</string>
    <string name="overview_mission_imposible">Fallout is the sixth sequel of the missionary action film series Mission: Impossible, starring Tom Cruise.In this mission impossible, IMF agent Ethan Hunt (Tom Cruise) was assigned to secure the three Russian plutonium cores stolen in Berlin from being sold by Apostles to fundamentalist John Lark. But his efforts to prevent this failed so that Hunts agents had to reclaim it.The film, directed by Christopher McQuarrie, managed to get a positive impression and was ranked 97% based on Rotten Tomatoes. Aired first in Paris on July 12, 2018, the film also produced by Tom Cruise has managed to earn revenues of up to $ 791 million, exceeding the production budget which only spent $ 178 million.</string>
    <string name="overview_ready_player_one">Ready Player One is a science fiction film genre with action adventure and live animation. The film, produced and directed by Steven Spielberg, is taken from the novel by Ernest Cline in 2011, and brings the events of 2045 when the earth has become dirty due to various pollution, corruption, climate change, and overpopulation.Meanwhile, some people are looking for escape by joining the OASIS virtual reality contest, where the winner who first finds the golden easter egg will get full ownership of the place. The film was released in America on March 29, 2018 and made an income of around $ 582 million, making it the 9th best-selling film in 2018</string>
    <string name="overview_the_meg">The Meg is a thriller action film with the element of horror Sci-Fi, which takes the story from the book Meg: A Novel of Deep Terror in 1997 by Steve Alten. The film tells the story of a sea captain and diving expert named Jonas Taylor, who was attacked by a giant megalodon shark with a length of 23 meters and made him leave half of his crew. The incident resulted in Jonas being dishonorably dishonored. However, he was again recruited on a mission to rescue Chinese scientists trapped in the Pacific Ocean to make amends The film, directed by Jon Turteltaub using the screenplay from Jon and Erich Hoeber and Dean Georgaris, premiered on August 10, 2018 and has grossed more than $ 527 million.</string>
    <string name="overview_aquaman">Aquaman is a Sci-Fi action adventure film taken from the DC Comics superhero character. The 6th film produced by DC Extended Universe has just premiered in London on November 26, 2018, and will be released in America on December 21, 2018.Aquaman tells the story of the super hero Arthur Curry who belonged to Atlantis and half human, but was reluctant to be the heir of the sea kingdom.</string>
    <string name="overview_jurassic_world">fallen Kingdom is a sequel to Jurassic World 2015, and becomes the fifth series of Jurassic Park film production. In the sequel this time, cast Dr. Ian Malcolm (Jeff Goldblum) will also repeat his role as in 1997.And still housed on the island of Isla Nublar, Central America, Owen Grady and Claire Dearing are trying to save the remaining dinosaurs before a volcanic eruption occurs.Sci-Fi adventure action film taken from the novel by Michael Crichton has managed to reap more than $ 1.3 billion since its first release in early June 2018. Thus, Jurassic World: Fallen Kingdom became the third best-selling film in 2018 and became a film the 12th best-selling of all time that passed the mark of up to billions of dollars.</string>
    <string name="overview_incredibles2">Incredibles 2 was released in America on June 15, 2018. The superhero film with this animated genre is a sequel to The Incredibles (2004). Authored and directed by Brad Bird, the film Incredibles 2 tells the story of Parrs family trying to restore public confidence in superheroes over the influence exerted by their new enemies, while he also tries to balance his family life. Played by Craig T. Nelson, Holly Hunter, Sarah Vowell, and Samuel L, the film Incredibles 2 received many positive responses for their voice acting, animation, score, and humor. In its opening weekend alone, Incredibles 2 was able to generate $ 182.7 million, and became the 4th best-selling film in 2018 with a total revenue of $ 1.2 billion worldwide.</string>
    <string name="overview_deadpool2">Deadpool 2 is an American superhero film written based on the Marvel Deadpool comic characters by Rob Liefeld and Fabian Nicieza. The film Deadpool 2 was released in America on May 18, 2018 and is a sequel to Deadpool (2016), as well as the continuation of the 11th series of X-Men films. In the film it is told that Deadpool formed an X-Force force to protect young mutants from a cybernetic soldier, Cable. Deadpool 2, directed by David Leitch using the Paul Wernick, Rhett Reese, and Ryan Reynolds screenplay, made a profit of more than $ 734 million, and became the 6th best-selling film in 2018. The film received many positive responses, especially in humor. And currently, the advanced edition of Deadpool 3 is still under development.</string>
    <string name="overview_star_wars">Solo is a Sci-Fi action film based on the Star Wars character Han Solo. The film, directed by Phil Lord and Christopher Miller before being fired and replaced by Ron Howard, is the second anthology film of Star Wars following Rogue One (2016). The story is told about the incident 10 years before A New Hope, and explores the beginning of the adventure of Han Solo with Chewbacca. This film project was made in January 2017, and only premiered in Los Angeles on May 10, 2018. Although many received positive responses in their acting and visual appearances. However, some critics judge if the films storyline is predictable. Being the first film in the Star Wars franchise, Solo: A Star War Story only generates $ 392.9 million worldwide.</string>
    <string name="overview_ant_man">Ant-Man and the Wasp is the MCUs 20th film, based on the superhero characters from the Marvel comics Scott Lang / Ant-Man and Hope van Dyne / Wasp by Stan Lee, Larry Lieber, Jack Kirby, and Wasp. In this film, Lang as Ant-Man collaborates with Hank Pym to save Janet van Dyne (the Wasp) from the quantum realm, even though the relationship between the two is in conflict. The Ant-Man and the Wasp film, directed by Peyton Reed, is a sequel to Ant-Man (2015), and became the 8th best-selling film in 2018. Ant-Man and the Wasp has grossed more than $ 622 million worldwide since it was released July 6, 2018 in the United States. The film also received many praises for its appearance, greed, and humor.</string>
    <string name="overview_predator">Predator is an American Sci-Fi action film that becomes the 4th continuation of the Predator film series, following Predator (1987), Predator 2 (1990), and Predators (2010). But according to the director and writer of the film (Shane Black), revealed that Predator 2018 is an \"inventive sequel\" that is different from Predator 2 and Predators, by carrying out more modern settings. The film begins when a predator ship falls to the earth and attacks the soldier Quinn McKenna and his team while on a hostage mission. Released theatrically in America on September 14, 2018, the 2018 Predator film received many reviews from critics, but earned more than $ 160 million worldwide</string>
    <string name="overview_skyscreper">Skyscraper is an American action film directed by Rawson Marshall Thurber, and stars one of them by Dwayne Johnson as Will Sawyer. This film tells the story of a former FBI agent (Will Sawyer) who must save his family from the worlds tallest skyscraper newly built, but burned and taken over by criminals. The Skyscraper film was released in America on July 13, 2018, and managed to earn more than $ 341 million with an initial production budget of $ 125 million. Although many critics praised Johnsons acting in the tense film, but not a few who consider that the film is a cliché and almost similar to the film Die Hard and The Towering Inferno.</string>
    <string name="overview_alpha">Alpha is an American historical adventure film that tells the story of survival in the last ice age that occurred 20,000 years ago. A young hunter played by Kodi Smit-McPhee must fight against nature to find a way home and make friends with an injured wolf. The film, directed by Albert Hughes, was released in America on August 17, 2018.</string>
    <string name="overview_oceans8">Oceans 8 is a robbery-themed comedy film which is a continuation and spin-off of the Steven Soderberghs Ocean trilogy. The film, written by Ross and Olivia Milch, tells the story of a group of women led by a sister from Danny Ocean (Debbie Ocean), played by Sandra Bullock. He planned a sophisticated theft at the annual Gala Met at the New York Metropolitan Museum of Art. Although Soderbergh did not intend to release a continuation of Ocean\'s Thirteen (2007), he went out of line with the release of the Ocean\'s 8 spin-off which was all played by women. The film was released in America on June 8, 2018 and managed to reap more than $ 296 million worldwide, although many received criticism of the storyline.</string>
    <string name="overview_bumblebee">Bumblebee is the 6th Sci-Fi action film from the continuation of the Transformers live action and prequel series from the Transformers series (2007). The film, directed by Travis Knight with a script from Christina Hodson, tells about the adventures of one autobot named Bumblebee in 1987, twenty years before the events in the first film. At that time Bumblebee was taking refuge on a small dock in the California coastal town. Charlie Watson, a teenage girl found it broken and broken, and realized that the object was not unusual. But they both eventually became fugitives of a government body called sector 7. For those of you who are waiting for the continuation of this Transformer series, you must be patient waiting for the release schedule on December 21, 2018</string>
    <string name="overview_strong">The film is also known by the title 12 Strong: The True Story of The Horse Soldiers, which is an action drama film titled war. The film 12 Strong is taken from a non-fiction book by Doug Stanton entitled Horse Soldiers. The film tells the story of CIA paramilitary officers and American special forces sent to Afghanistan right after the September 11 attacks. The film, released in the United States on January 19, 2018, received many mixed criticisms and only got a 53% rating based on 148 reviews. Some critics praised the solid acting of the players and the thrilling plot of the story. But he regretted the execution of his individual, and less see the history of the Afghanistan War, and the disappointing feel of the film.</string>
    <string name="overview_alita_battle_angel">Alita: Battle Angel is an American action film with a cyberpunk theme and is based on the story characters in the manga Battle Angel Alita, by Yukito Kishiro. The film was originally scheduled for release on July 20, 2018, but was postponed and rescheduled on February 14, 2019. The film tells the story of a female cyborg rescued by scientists in a rubbish dump in the 26th century. The film, which adapted anime from the first few books of Battle Angel, tells of future events, where robots and cyborgs are common. And in a floating city called Tiphares, there are many dark secrets and often throw trash into the city below. In the city below, a scientist named Ido pawed and found a cyborg which was later given the name Alita.</string>
    <string name="overview_robin_hood">Robin Hood is an adventure action film based on the story of Robin Hood. The film was directed by Otto Bathurst with a script by Ben Chandler and David James Kelly. In this film, Robin Hood, who has just returned from a crusade, joins the Moorish commander in a revolt against the corrupt British crown. Since it was released November 21, 2018, this film received many negative criticisms. Many sources compare it to the film King Arthur: Legend of the Sword (2007). Some critics also criticize the narration, the direction of the film, and also the waste of players. With a production cost of around $ 100 million, the film only grossed $ 22 million. But choreography, romance, and exploitation of a sharp battlefield, will spoil you against the legendary Robin Hood story.</string>

    <string name="title_teen_titans">TeenTitans</string>
    <string name="overview_teen_titans">There\'s no shortage of laughs and action in this series based on the DC characters of the same name. Since it premiered on Cartoon Network back in 2003, Teen Titans has become the most beloved series on the network. Apart from the laughs and action, Teen Titans manages to tackle serious themes and handle character development like no other animated series could. The series had a five-season run, with reruns continuing to air on the network to this day. Younger generations stumble upon the show and fall in love with it much like previous watchers did almost 15 years ago.</string>
    <string name="title_dexters">dexter\'s Laboratory</string>
    <string name="overview_dexters">There\'s something absolutely adorable about this tiny boy genius and all the inventions he comes up with in his secret laboratory. Dexter\'s Laboratory was just one of those shows that made you laugh for no reason. The relationship that Dexter had with his sister Dee Dee was one of the highlights of the show, and of course, the competition with fellow genius Mandark was just as good. Dexter\'s constant battles are the stuff of comedy. While he may be highly intelligent, his carelessness and overexcitement takes over most of the time, making him fail miserably at what he does. The best part about this show is Dexter\'s extremely thick accent despite the fact that he comes from an all-American family.</string>
    <string name="title_powerpuff">Powerpuff Girls</string>
    <string name="overview_powerpuff">Blossoms, Bubbles, and Buttercup were the perfect combinations of sugar, spice, and everything nice. The superpowered trio always managed to save the day from all the criminals using their abilities. They may have been tiny, but they were packed with powers. Blossom, the leader, could freeze anything with her breath. Bubbles, the sweetest of the three girls, could emit sonic waves. Lastly, Buttercup was the toughest fighter. Although she lacked a unique ability, she made up for it with tons of fighting will and strength.</string>
    <string name="title_courage">Courage The Cowardly Dog</string>
    <string name="overview_courage">Here\'s another scary-themed CN show that was more hilarious than spooky. The main character of the series, Courage, was such a great character that it was really able to carry the entire series on its own. Maybe it was because it was pink and completely human-like, but Courage was entertaining to watch. The dog and the elderly couple he was living with somehow kept finding themselves in bizarre situations involving the paranormal. Given that he\'s not the most courageous creature, Courage still manages to protect his owners no matter what it took</string>
    <string name="title_adventure_time">Adventure Time</string>
    <string name="overview_adventure_time">if you\'re looking for true adventure in the most literary sense of the word, Adventure Time might be the show for you. This show is about the post-apocalyptic lives of a young boy, Finn, and his adoptive brother dog Jake. Jake had the magical abilities to transform into any shape whenever he wanted to. They live in the Land of Ooo, quite the fantastical land that\'s reminiscent of various video games. In fact, the entire show feels very much like a video game being played out. It adds to the charm of the show.</string>
    <string name="title_samurai_jack">Samurai Jack</string>
    <string name="overview_samurai_jack">It\'s odd enough that the samurai in the show has a Western name, Jack, but his adventures were some of the best ever. Jack was sent into a dystopian future to fight a shape-shifting enemy, Aku. Aku was set to take over the world much like all tyrannical villains that were ever created, and Jack was set to stop him in his tracks. The show premiered in 2001 and lasted for five seasons. Samurai Jack was so good that it won a total of eight Primetime Emmy Awards, and that\'s not even including all the other awards and nominations it received during its run.</string>
    <string name="title_tom_jerry">Tom And Jerry</string>
    <string name="overview_tom_jerry">Talk about going classic, Tom and Jerry is one of the most classic cartoon favorites there ever was. We all know the whole cat-and-mouse chase premise of the story, yet no matter how many times we watch the cartoon, it never fails to make us laugh. Tom and Jerry was created back in 1940, and the central story is the rivalry between the two characters. There were times when they\'d be amicable, but that was almost always short-lived. The cartoon featured no dialogue whatsoever, which added to its magic and charm altogether.</string>
    <string name="title_regular_show">Regular Show</string>
    <string name="overview_regular_show">This is one of the newer show on this list being that it first aired in 2010 and ended just last year in 2017. Regular show is the story of two working class friends, Mordecai and Rigby. Mordecai was a blue jay, while Rigby was a raccoon. In every episode, the two friends would go about their day and usually would have a simple problem to contend with. However, their days almost always end up including some type of bizarre adventure. The show\'s viewership during its peak was at 2 to 2.5 million viewers each week—a true testament to just how good the show was.</string>
    <string name="title_scooby">Scooby-Doo</string>
    <string name="overview_scooby">Scooby-Doo is one of those shows that will just last forever. So many remakes of the original have sprouted, and the idea behind the stories was just so unique. There\'s no stop to just how many different storylines can be created. This is proven by the fact that Scooby-Doo first aired in 1969 and is still continuing on to this day in various formats. Scooby-Doo is also one of the most iconic characters ever created along with the rest of the gang: Fred, Daphne, Velma, and of course, Shaggy.</string>
    <string name="title_pokemon">Pokemon</string>
    <string name="overview_pokemon">Perhaps one of the most successful franchises in anime, Pokemon is the series based on the Japanese anime phenomenon Pocket Monsters. It tells the story of 10-year old Ash Ketchum and his journey to becoming a Pokémon master. His first ever Pokemon is Pikachu; and although their relationship had a rough start, they become the best of friends to this day. Their adventures along the way are both fun and treacherous, as they fight off various villains and evil Pokemon. Pokemon\'s success thrives in the show and various other forms of media and entertainment.</string>
    <string name="title_loony_tunes">Loony Tunes</string>
    <string name="overview_loony_tunes">A series of short films make up the Looney Tunes cartoons, and it brought us some of the most famous characters in the entire world and history of animation. During the golden age of American animation from 1930 to 1969, we were introduced to characters such as Bugs Bunny, Daffy Duck, Tweety, Sylvester, Porky Pig, Elmer Fudd, Yosemite Sam, Road Runner, Wile E. Coyote, Tasmanian Devil, Speedy Gonzales, and a few more. For many, these characters are reminiscent of Saturday morning laughs and endless entertainment. Looney Tunes are as timeless as animation can get.</string>
    <string name="title_ben10">Ben 10</string>
    <string name="overview_ben10">Ben Tennyson conquers the outer space in the series, Ben 10. The 10-year old gets a hold of an alien device known as the Omnitrix; he puts it on like a watch, and then he transforms into whatever alien creature he may need to be in order to fight a villain in space. As exciting as that may sound, it took a while for Ben 10 to pick up momentum. It became popular eventually, even spawning a few other shows to become a franchise. The show lasted for four seasons from 2005 until 2008.</string>
    <string name="title_gumbal">The Amazing World Of Gumbal</string>
    <string name="overview_gumbal">There are a few characters out there that truly capture the imagination of children. 12-year old Gumball Watterson and his best friend and adoptive brother Darwin were some of coolest characters in cartoon in most recent times. Gumball happens to be a blue cat while Darwin is a goldfish. The two are middle school kids who live and attend school in the city of Elmore. The show is basically about the daily lives of the two kids and the people around them and all the troubles they get themselves into. It\'s a refreshing take on just everyday lives—something that some kids find relatable versus shows that are about villains and superpowers.</string>
    <string name="title_chowder">Chowder</string>
    <string name="overview_chowder">Not many cartoon take upon the culinary world as its topic, but that\'s exactly what Chowder is all about. Chowder is the main character of the show. He\'s a young apprentice in Chef Mung Daal\'s catering company. He\'s described as a scatterbrain, so he always somehow manages to get himself into trouble. He also gets into trouble because of his hearty appetite. The show may have been short-lived with only 3 seasons and a total of 49 episodes, but it was still good enough to get at least one Primetime Emmy Award during that time.</string>
    <string name="title_justice">Young Justice</string>
    <string name="overview_justice">An adaptation of DC Universe\'s characters, Young Justice was about the lives of the superheroes; only in this show the superheroes were still in their teenage years. The superheroes featured in this show included Batman, Aquaman, Flash, Green Arrow, and their proteges, Robin, Aqualad, Kid Flash, and Speedy. This was another short-lived success, having only lasted for 2 seasons. But there\'s a new development coming to the show that might end up with the release of a third season this year.</string>

    <string name="tab_text_1">Movies</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">TV Shows</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">Katalog Film2</string>
    <string name="change_language_settings">Change Language Settings</string>
</resources>
